## **PROFILE**

I'm a software engineer based in Shanghai China, MA specializing in developing and monitoring exceptional, high-quality websites, web applications, and Wechat Mini Programs. I have 3+ years of experience as а software engineer, Team Lead, and Project manager. mostly working using JavaScript and its major framework and libraries. mostly of my work is frontend related which based on Single applications, analytics dashboard, Data visualization, Progressive web application and Wechat mini programs' have strong knowledge of backend development and i have worked on database design. RFST and SOAP API architectures for Web applications, mobile applications, Blockchain and IOT based projects.

#### CONTACT

Wechat/Phone 18621549424

WEBSITE:

<u>Portfolio</u>

FMAII:

marahmanis@gmail.com

## **HOBBIES**

- Programming
- Reading
- Swimming
- Running
- Hiking

# **Muhammad Anis Ur Rahman**

Software Engineer

#### **EDUCATION**

# **BS Software Engineer**

University Of Swat (Pakistan)

2013 - 2017

BS Software Engineering (BSSE) degree to fulfil the need of the growing software market. The program has been designed to produce professionals who have excellent problem solving skills and can solve complex computational problems by critically thinking and analysing the problems. The curriculum provides well-adjusted mix of basic science, technology, linguistics and business related areas to produce graduate capable of holding leadership position both in research and non-academic sectors.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Software Engineer**

ShareIN Shanghai (China) November 2018– Current

- Product Development.
- API development and Integration.
- Dashboard Development.
- Progressive web applications.
- Unit/integration Testing.
- Algorithm Implementation.
- Payment Gateways Like Alipay Wechat Pay
- Wechat Mini Programs

### **Software Engineer**

Freshchefs Shanghai (China) Apr 2018– October 2018

- Web Application Development.
- Food delivery system development.
- Reservation Integration.
- Payment Gateways Like Alipay Wechat Pay
- Wechat Mini Programs

#### Software Engineer (Intern)

Lahore (Pakistan) Aug 2017– March 2018

- Document and test new software applications.
- Assess new application ideas.
- Research competitor offerings.
- Develop applications (coding, programming)
- Interview beta testers.

# **LANGUAGES**

- English
- Arabic
- Pashto
- Urdu
- Chinese

## **INTREST**

- Blockchain
- Entrepreneurship
- Learning Chinese
- Python
- Data Science

<u>Stackoverflow</u>

Linkedin

<u>Github</u>

## **SKILLS**

Mostly focused on web development and hybrid mobile application development have given me a perfect grip on most of JavaScript frameworks. following are my key skills:

- HTML5/WXML
- CSS3/WXSS/SCSS
- Bootstrap 3/4
- Material design
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Angular 1.x
- Vue JS/Vuex/Nuxt/Vue-router
- React JS/Redux
- Vuetify/Ant Design/Iview
- NativeScript
- Node JS
- Express/Koa/Sails
- Loopback
- Web Sockets
- Webpacks
- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- Postgres
- Sequelize
- PWA
- Wechat Mini Programs

# **PROJECTS**

Please visit my Portfolio to check my latest work